Guide to the Edward Bradford Titchener papers,1887-1940.
Titchener, Edward Bradford papers, 1887-1940
- Correspondence
  - EBT to Tice & Lynch, 2/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 2/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Prof. E. G. Boring, 2/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Leonard J. Carmichael, 2/6/25 (Box 6)
  - Martha Sanf ord to EBT, 2/7/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 2/7/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Kelson, 2/7/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to W. D. Lighthall, 2/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mrs.. W. F. Frear, 2/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Marion Monroe, 2/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Carroll C. Pratt, 2/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. F. H. Ward, 2/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Sanford, 2/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Scientific International Research Service Corp., 2/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Sahford, 2/10/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/10/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. L. Clements, 2/10/25 (Box 6)
  - Stanley Clarke to EBT, 2/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor F. Krueger, 2/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Carl Murchison, 2/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. Shearer Stirl, 2/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Harold K. Schzelderup, 2/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 2/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H, 2/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Karl Dallenbach, 2/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. A. Poynder, 2/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Karl Marbe, 2/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Sanford, 2/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H, 2/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to R. M. Ogden, 2/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to J. A. Barth, 2/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Leonard Carmichael, 2/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Williams Electric Company, 2/14/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 2/14/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Warren, 2/14/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company (enclosed manuscript of book review), 2/14/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to F. B. Fiske, 2/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr. Henry Chapman, 2/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Carl Murchison, 2/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Sanford, 2/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Sadazi Takahi, 2/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Martin Reymert, 2/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Helen Bateman, 2/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to "H", 2/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. A. Poynder, 2/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to C. J. Rumsey and Co., 2/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to University of Pennsylvania Bulletin, 2/18/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Sanford, 2/18/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Hew York Life Insurance Company, 2/18/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to the Librarian, University of Toronto, 2/18/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Otto Klemm, 2/18/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. Keatly Moore, 2/18/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor J. Franklin Walker, 2/18/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Florence B. Woolsey, 2/18/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor August Kirschmann, 2/18/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor J. R. Kantor, 2/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. H. B. Brower, 2/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Casper L. Redfield, 2/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. C. S. Myers, 2/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor D. S. Robinson, 2/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to F. J. Wylie, 2/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Frank Thilly, 2/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor W. Wirth, 2/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Meenes, 2/20/25 (Box 6)
  - RBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/20/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 2/20/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Bishop, 2/21/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Rogers, 2/21/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to George L. Coleraan, 2/21/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 2/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor R. M. Ogden, 2/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Nafe, 2/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Robert McMurry, 2/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. T. Lines, 2/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. Keatley Moore, 2/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Purchasing Department Morrill Hall, 2/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Elisabeth, 2/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. Rowland Wood, 2/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Office of the Director General of Archeology in India, 2/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 2/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. Miles A. Tinker, 2/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Brown and Delavan, 2/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. W. A. Boyd, 2/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. H. B. Davis, 2/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 2/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. E. Howe, 2/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 2/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. James Clapham, 2/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. L.N. Wilson, 3/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor F. Stuart Chapin, 3/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to MR.. W. A. Boyd, 3/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Leonard Carmichael, 3/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E, G. Boring, 3/2/25 (Box 6)
  - Isabelle Hackett to EBT, 3/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 3/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Hoisington, 3/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Nafe, 3/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. David Wechsler, 3/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. M. R. Terr, 3/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Sangfeld, 3/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. C. Warren, 3/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Mario Puglisi, 3/4/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 3/4/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 3/4/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor R. W. Wilcocks, 3/4/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 3/4/25 (Box 6)
  - Johann Earth to EBT German, 3/5/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor S. W. Fernberger, 3/5/25 (Box 6)
  - SBT to Dr. H. B. Davis, 3/5/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor L. C. Marshall, 3/5/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 3/5/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor W. F. Book, 3/5/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 3/5/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 3/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor K. Marbe, 3/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 3/7/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Tice and Lynch, 3/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Trans-Lux Daylight Picture Screen Inc., 3/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to W. B. Saunders Compapy, 3/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Bixley, 3/10/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Kate T. Bush, 3/10/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss. Louise O'Connell, 3/10/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 3/10/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor F. Kiesow, 3/10/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. C. Southall, 3/10/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Max Meenes, 3/10/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor W. Heinrich, 3/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to "H", 3/11/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 3/14/25 (Box 6)
  - Davis Tuck to EBT, 3/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor W. Heinrich (encl. memorandum re Titchener by H. P. Weld), 3/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to "H", 3/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor George Miller, 3/21/25 (Box 6)
  - [ ? ] von Kluge to EBT, 3/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 3/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Journal de Psychologie, 3/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 3/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. S. H. Self, 3/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 3/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbuty, 3/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor M. Matsumoto, 3/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. T. Lines, 3/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 3/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor W. S. Foster, 3/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. C. L. Shaw, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to C. H. Douglas, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to P. H. Ward, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Walter Hunter, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor S. W. Fernberger, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. A. Poynder, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. B. Davis, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to W. Wideman, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. fangfeld, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to "H", 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 3/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Kelson, 3/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dixon and Robinson, 3/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor R. M. Ogden, 3/37/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. F. B. Baker, 3/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Earl Marbe, 3/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor William Burhham, 3/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 3/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Thomas L. Elder, 3/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Margaret Wylie, 3/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 3/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 3/30/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Gilbert Rich, 3/30/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 3/30/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to "F", 3/30/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Ballenbach, 3/31/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Elisabeth, 3/31/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 3/31/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Nafe, 3/31/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 3/31/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Wakeman, 3/31/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Kahn Foundation, 3/31/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company (end. evaluation of manuscript), 4/l/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Sanford, 4/l/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 4/l/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Philip Hausmann, 4/l/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 4/l/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. C. Wilson Smith, 4/l/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Beagil Company, 4/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor K. Koffka, 4/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to R. W. Sailor, 4/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Elma J. Bailey, 4/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Edgar Doll, 4/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to W. Wideman, 4/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 4/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. Scotter of J. B, Lippincott Company, 4/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 4/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor William Bumham, 4/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to F. C. Bartlett, 4/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. P. Weld, 4/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Sanford, 4/4/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 4/4/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Prof essor William Barry, 4/4/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 4/4/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. C. Warren copy of remarks by Howard C. Warren, 4/4/25 (Box 6)
  - Kierow to EBT, 4/12/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor R. A. Tsanoff, 4/12/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Gilbert Rich, 4/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. F. H. Ward, 4/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. W. Wideman, 4/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to the President of Hood College, 4/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Elsie Murray, 4/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor R, H. Tsanoff, 4/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The President of Rice University, 4/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to John Zybura, 4/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to G. H. Taylor, 4/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor S. Eldridge, 4/14/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. & L.S. Rowe, 4/14/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Linwood Eisenberg, 4/14/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to G. T. lines, 4/14/25 (Box 6)
  - Johann Earth to EBT German, 4/15/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren untitled, 4/15/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Albert Kunty, 4/15/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dalleribach, 4/15/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to "H", 4/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Baker, 4/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr. Uiley Boone, 4/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to George Alien and Unwin Ltd., 4/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to James P. C. Southall, 4/18/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 4/20/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to James P. C. Southall, 4/21/25 (Box 6)
  - Herbert Langfeld to EBT, 4/23/25 (Box 6)
  - Howland Wood to EBT, 4/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Houghton Mifflin and Co., 4/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Douglas Fryer, 4/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Earl Rudisill, 4/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor C. A. Ruckmick, 4/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. P. Weld, 4/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Marion W. Nagle, 4/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to E. H. Tifcchener, 4/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor K. Marbe, 4/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor K. Marbe, 4/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to D. C. Heath and Co, 4/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 4/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 4/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to William Hesslein, 4/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Seth Wakeman, 4/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Ranfeld, 4/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Edward S. Bobinson, 4/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Howard C. Warren, 4/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. T. Lines, 4/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor W. Koehler, 4/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to "F", 4/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 4/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Hulsey Cason, 4/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Leonard J. Canaichael, 4/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to D. C. Heath and Company, 4/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. W. M. Carley, 4/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 4/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 4/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. L. H. Wilson, 4/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. A. Binder, 4/29/25 (Box 6)
  - Dr. L. N. Wilson to EBT, 4/30/25 (Box 6)
  - BBT to Professor E. R. Jaensch, 4/30/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, 4/30/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. L. B. Hoisington, 4/30/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. P. Weld, 4/30/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Helson, 5/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor M. J. Zigler, 5/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. R. C. Yotmg, 5/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. S. Robinson, 5/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 5/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to F. E. Johnson, 5/2/25 (Box 6)
  - Herbert Langfeld to EBT, 5/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Seth Wakerman, 5/6/25 (Box 6)
  - Carl Murchison to EBT, 5/8/25 (Box 6)
  - Wolfgang Kohler to EBT, 5/12/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor R. W. Wilcocks, 5/15/25 (Box 6)
  - H ? Bartlett to EBT, 5/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Diramick, 5/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Treasury Department, 5/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 5/21/25 (Box 6)
  - Isabelle Hackett to EBT, 5/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring - 2nd page missing, 5/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Seth Wakeman, 5/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to A. B. Recknagel, 5/22/25 (Box 6)
  - Manuscript by H. F. Verwoerd - belongs w/ letter of 6/4/25 as an enclosure, 5/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Will Hulin, 5/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Earl Rudisill, 5/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to W. B. Pillsbury, 5/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to the Treasury Department, 5/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 5/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to F. L. Dimmick, 5/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. P. Weldt, 5/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Edward Barrett, 5/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Leonard Carmichael, 5/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 5/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Rose S. Malmud, 5/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Kelson, 5/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Henry T. Moore, 5/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to "H", 5/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 5/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. L. F. Carrow of American Railway Express Co., 5/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Madison Bentley, 5/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor A. B. Recknagel, 5/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Helson, 5/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Wilder Bancroft, 5/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor A. A. Schaeffer, 5/27/25 (Box 6)
  - Mario Guglisi to EBT, 5/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor M. F. Washburn [Margaret Floy], 5/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 5/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 5/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Ida M. Heller, 5/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Elisabeth F. Holler, 5/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mfc. Theodore Schroeder, 5/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. Daniels, Hotel Buffalo, 5/29/25 (Box 6)
  - Professor G. Heymans to EBT, 5/?)/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 6/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Heinrich Kluver, 6/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 6/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to F. L. Dimmick, 6/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Bixley, 6/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. BoringS, 6/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 6/1/25 (Box 6)
  - L. N. Wilson to EBT, 6/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Director, the Lincoln School, N. Y. C, 6/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor John A. McGeoch, 6/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to the Manager, Hotel Buffalo, Buffalo, N.Y., 6/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 6/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Sade Takaki, 6/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Department of Psychology, Stanford University, 6/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 6/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Thomas L Elder, 6/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. C. J. Warden, 6/3/25 (Box 6)
  - R.W. Wilcocks to EBT, 6/V25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Kiss Dorothy R. Knight, 6/5/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. P. Bussell Bichowsky, 6/5/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. S. H. Self, 6/5/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Comptroller, Cornell University, 6/5/25 (Box 6)
  - G. Stoerring to EBT, 6/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBB to Professor Madison Bentley, 6/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. Clements, 6/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 6/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 6/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Paul S. Livermore, 6/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Lillian Hatfield, 6/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Lanffeld, 6/6/35 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor G. Stoerring, 6/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. R. W. Sailor, 6/8/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to C. J. Warden, 6/8/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor R. M. Ogden, 6/8/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor N. Schmidt, 6/8/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Ogden, 6/8/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 6/8/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Karl Hilzinger, 6/8/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to William Hesslein, 6/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dorothy Cole, 6/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, 6/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Elisabeth, 6/9/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor A. P. Weiss, 6/12/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 6/12/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Kate Bush, 6/12/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to M. L. Reymert, 6/12/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 6/l2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Hiss Goldie Blum, 6/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 6/13/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 6/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Edith Baker, 6/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Hamilton B. Wood, 6/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Isabella Hackett, 6/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Treman King and Co., 6/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 6/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. F. L. Wells, 6/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mario Puglisi, 6/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. B. Davis, 6/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Miles I. Tinker, 6/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 6/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Leonard Carmichael, 6/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Kellogg's Teachers' Agency, 6/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 6/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr. Thomas L. Elder, 6/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor F. L. Dinndek, 6/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor M. L. Reymert, 6/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. dements, 6/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 6/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 6/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mansbach Cigar Co., 6/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Co. (end. manuscript), 6/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to W. S. Hunter, 6/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 6/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 6/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. Charles C. Thomas, 6/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Presley D. Stout, 6/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. James E. Ives, 6/84/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor W. Radecki, 6/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. Philip Johnson, 6/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to T. L. Elder, 6/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 6/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Department of Psychology University of Pennsylvania, 6/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 6/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to L. T. Morgan, 6/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Fisk Teachers Agency, 6/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Southern Teachers Agency, 6/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 6/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 6/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 6/29/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. F. L. Dimnick, 7/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor L. W. Cole, 7/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to E. R. Smith, 7/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor G. Stoering, 7/1/25 (Box 6)
  - H. ?. Bartflett to EBT, 7/1/25 (Box 6)
  - Howland Wood to EBT, 7/3/25 (Box 6)
  - George Brett to EBT, 7/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor R. W. Wilcocks, 7/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 7/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to J. W. Clark, 7/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl DaHenbach, 7/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor W. Heinrieh, 7/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to George Brett, 7/3/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. H. Helson, 7/8/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Charles C. Thomas, 7/8/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Sargents, 7/10/25 (Box 6)
  - George Brett to EBT, 7/14/25 (Box 6)
  - Sargents to EBT, 7/21/25 (Box 6)
  - E. G. Boring to EBT, 7/23/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 7/24/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Dorothy Knight, 7/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. R. R. Smith, The Macmillan Company, 7/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. C. S. Myers, 7/31/25 (Box 6)
  - Thomas Elder to EBT, 8/7/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor Winifred Hyde, 8/10/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Harry Helson, 8/12/25 (Box 6)
  - Christine Ladd - Franklin to EBT, 8/16/25 (Box 6)
  - R. R. Smith of Macmillan to EBT, 8/25/25 (Box 6)
  - C. C. Parker to EBT, 8/25/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to George Law, 8/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. G. J. Rich, 8/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. S. Daniel House, 8/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to R. H. Gault, 8/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 8/27/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to G. T. Lines, 8/28/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to C. C. Parker, 8/29/25 (Box 6)
  - T. A. Hunter to EBT, 9/17/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Edward Bafrett, 9/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckmick, 9/26/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckmick, 10/1/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 10/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to R. E. Treman, 10/2/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Arthur MacDonald, 10/6/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 10/7/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 10/7/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor K. Koffka, 10/8/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor F. L. Dimmick, 10/14/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Ballenbach, 10/15/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor A. L. Kroeber, 10/15/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. W. W. Carley, 10/15/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Max Kohl, 10/15/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. W. Wideman, 10/15/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 10/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. E. Barrett, 10/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 10/16/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor M. L. Reymert, 10/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 10/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 10/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 10/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Dr. Weld, 10/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to J. P. Guilford, 10/19/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Katl Dallenbach, 10/20/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Miss Mae Kilgaimon, 10/20/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 10/20/25 (Box 6)
  - Karl Dallenbach to EBT, 10/21/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor H. G. Bishop, 10/21/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor B. C. Rogers, 10/21/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Department of Psychology, Stanford University, California, 10/21/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Mt. F. H. Ward, 10/21/25 (Box 6)
  - Karl Dalleribach to EBT, 10/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dalleribach, 10/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dalleribach, 10/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor T. A. Hunter, 10/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Professor R. W. Wilcocks, 10/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBB to Professor J. A. Highsmith, 10/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 10/22/25 (Box 6)
  - EBT to Chairman of Summer session, 10/22/25 (Box 6)
  - Karl Daneribach to EBT, 10/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Karl Daneribach, 10/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. G. Baring, 10/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. W. Thomas Shepherd, 10/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. F. H. Lund, 10/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Edmund Jacobson, 10/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Robert C. Astrop, 10/23/25 (Box 7)
  - Karl Dalleribach to EBT, 10/26/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Karl Dalleribach, 10/26/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to B. H. Stoelling, 10/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. H. Kluver, 10/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Otto Klemm, 10/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to T. G. Miller's Sons papier co., 10/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Editor, University of Iowa Studies, 10/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Francis Ford, 10/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mrs. Ladd Franklin, 10/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 10/28/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 10/28/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 10/28/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Albert Andre, 10/28/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Raymond H. Wheeler, 10/28/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to MR.. G. T. Lines, 10/28/25 (Box 7)
  - Karl Dallenbach to EBT, 10/29/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 10/29/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Horace T. C. Tu, 10/29/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Robert Astrop, 10/29/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 10/29/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 10/30/25 (Box 7)